arqspin.com 2016-04-14

# Privacy Policy - Arqspin

## Arqspin Privacy Policy

We at Arqball LLC have a firm commitment to safeguarding your privacy. This page will inform you about our information gathering and dissemination practices. When we refer to “Arqball”, we are referring to this website and to Arqball LLC and its affiliates. Welcome to our website.

PLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY STATEMENT CAREFULLY. We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting any personal information you share with us through this website. This privacy policy statement (“Privacy Policy”) explains how we collect personal information about you through this website and how this information is then used or disclosed. It does not apply to our websites that do not display or link to this Privacy Policy or that have their own Privacy Policy or to information we may collect from you or about you in other ways, including through emails you may send to us. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any party.

Generally, we gather information about you to provide you with convenient access to certain features and services and to verify your identity in our interactions with you, to deliver a better customer service experience, to administer our business, and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy and on our website. For example, before you may submit any content to our website, we ask that you create an account and sign in with a login name and password. If you choose not to provide us with the requested information, you will not be able to submit any material to our website or use our services because we cannot verify your identity.

We hope that this Privacy Policy will remove any concerns you may have about supplying us with information and make visiting this website a rewarding and safe experience. We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time in our sole discretion by posting the updated terms on this website. You are responsible for periodically reading this Privacy Policy. Your continued usage of this website and our services after we have updated this Privacy Policy means you have read the updated terms and agree with such changes. This Privacy Policy is not intended to and does not create any contractual or other legal right in or on behalf of any person.

This Privacy Policy describes how we treat the following types of information:

  * “Personally Identifiable Information” means information that can identify or be traced to an individual person, such as your name, date and place of birth, home address, telephone number, email address, Social Security number, and credit card number.
  * “Non-Personal Information” means information that cannot, without further information, be traced to an individual person, such as the aggregation of information such as the total number of users over a certain age or geographic location.
  * “Information” means Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personal Information.

### Personally Identifiable Information We Collect and How it is Used

Personally Identifiable Information we collect on our website may include: (i) your name, address, contact information such as email address and phone number, age, gender, country of residence, and user profile, which we use for account administration and communications purposes; (ii) financial and payment information for fulfilling purchases; (iii) a username, which can be your real name or an alias, to track your activities on our website, for administrative purposes and to communicate with you; and (iv) a network address used to identify your personal computer.

You can access most portions of the website without entering Personally Identifiable Information and without expressly having to give consent to any specific question (beyond complying with the Terms and Conditions of the website). We do not collect any Personally Identifiable information about you through this website unless you choose to provide it to us voluntarily.

“Opting-In” is the process by which you expressly indicate that you want to participate in our service or one of its features or options. Generally, we use Personally Identifiable Information to respond to, process, and fulfill your requests, and update you on status. To submit material to the website and use our services, you will be asked to create an account with us. To Opt-In to our service, you would click the Create Account button which can be accessed via the Sign In link in the upper left hand corner of your screen. If you create an account with us, you will be asked to enter your name, billing and shipping address, phone number, and email address. If you want to obtain our paid services, we require that you provide payment information such as a bank account or credit card information, and other information as required by our third party processors.

“Opting-Out” is the process by which you expressly indicate that you decline to receive newsletters and other communications from us, excluding email concerning your account. To discontinue your receipt of such newsletters and communications, you can do so in the “Account Settings” portion of the “My Account” section of the website or you can send an email with your request to support@arqball.com.

If you do provide us with Personally Identifiable Information, we will only use it for the purposes described where it is collected or in this Privacy Policy. We may also use your postal mail or email address or phone number to send you further information about Arqball, or to contact you for the purposes of research, product development, or customer service. We may also aggregate personal and other information about you collected from this website with other information you provide us through interactions with you through the telephone or otherwise. If you encounter a screen or page that requests information you do not want to share with us, do not enter the information and do not proceed with that screen or page.

Arqball will not sell, license, transmit or disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties unless: (1) you expressly authorize us to do so; (2) it is necessary to enable third-party providers of products and services available on this website to respond to, process and fulfill your requests; (3) it is necessary to allow our trusted service providers or agents to provide services for us; (4) we do so in order to provide our products or services to you; (5) it is in connection with a sale of all or substantially all of the assets of Arqball or the merger of Arqball into another entity or any consolidation, share exchange, combination, reorganization, or like transaction in which Arqball is not the survivor; (6) as otherwise required or permitted by law, regulation, search warrant, subpoena or court order; or (7) we reasonably determine that it is necessary in order to protect the rights, property, or safety of Arqball, its users, or the public.

We will not disclose your personal information to a third party for their direct marketing purposes unless you first affirmatively agree to the disclosure.

### Non-Personal Information We Collect and How it is Used

As is true of most websites, we gather technical information about your interaction with our website automatically, and store it in our logs. Such information includes Internet Protocol addresses, web browser type, host or service provider, referring or exit pages, operating system, and date and time stamps.

And, as is true of most websites, we use Cookies and Web Beacons (both defined and described below) to collect or store Non-Personal Information about your use of our website. “Cookies” are a random and anonymous number assigned to visitors or websites. This file holds information such as how many times visitors are accessing our website, information concerning purchases or requests, validation information for members-only sections, and which sections of the website are most popular. This random number is kept in a small file that is sent to your browser and stored on your personal computer. Cookies are commonly used by online services to improve the user experience and have not been known to transmit computer viruses or otherwise harm your computer. Many Cookies last only through a single website session, or visit. Others may have an expiration date, or may remain on your computer until you delete them. Our Cookies will track only your activity relating to your online activity on this website, and will not track your other Internet activity. You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. However, if you choose to reject Cookies, you may not be able to use or access certain pages of this website or certain of our features, products or services.

We may occasionally use other companies to set Cookies on our website and gather Cookie information for us. In some cases, we may also use another company to operate web servers or process credit card purchases for our website. We use the Cookie information gathered by these companies in the same manner as stated above. In some cases, we retain both the Cookie information and/or the information you provide to us online – for example, to complete a transaction you requested or to keep historical records of your past transactions. In other cases, we only retain the Cookie and/or online information you give us at your request for your use in subsequent sessions.

“Web Beacons” are very small, often transparent, graphic electronic images that may be placed on our website to monitor your behavior on our website and to identify your interaction with our and third-party websites over time.

The information collected by Cookies and/or Web Beacons helps us to:

  1. provide you with a more customized experience on our website and greater convenience each time you interact with us;
  2. make it easier for you to use different parts of our website without having to login multiple times;
  3. help us understand which parts of our website are the most popular and how much time our users spend in each;
  4. store your preferences for certain kinds of information;
  5. measure the effectiveness of our communications, promotional campaigns, and the searches performed on our website;
  6. administer our website;
  7. develop statistics on any advertisements displayed on our websites; and
  8. study aggregate demographic information about our users as a whole.

### How We Protect Your Information

We restrict access to Information collected about you through our website to our employees, our affiliates’ employees, or others who need to know this Information to provide services to you or in the course of administering and conducting our business. We maintain appropriate physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect Information. We protect our database with various physical, technical and procedural measures and we restrict access to your Information by unauthorized persons. We also advise our employees about their responsibility to protect customer information and we provide our employees with appropriate guidelines for adhering to our business ethics standards and policies.

You should also help us protect your Information by:

  1. using only secure web browsers;
  2. employing common anti-virus and anti-malware tools on your system to keep it safe;
  3. carefully logging out after using our website;
  4. using strong password with a combination of letters and numbers;
  5. changing your password often;
  6. protecting your username and password; and
  7. notifying us immediately via email at support@arqball.com if you feel your login and/or password have been compromised.

Finally, please exercise discretion and use caution with respect to your Personal Identifiable Information. We may provide public areas on our website where you can post information about yourself and others. We do not control who reads postings on our website, or how they may use or disclose such information. If you choose to voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on public portions of our website, that information will be publicly available and can be collected and used by others. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages.

### Update and Verify Information We Have About You

If you create an account with us, you can review and maintain your account information at anytime, by logging in to your account or submitting a request to support@arqball.com. In addition, you may request a copy of the information that we currently hold about you by sending a detailed email to support@arqball.com with all specifics necessary for us to consider and respond to your request.

### Third Party Links

This website may contain links to third party websites. While we endeavor to work with third parties that share our respect for user privacy, we are not responsible for the websites or privacy practices of such third parties. We do not endorse these parties, their content, or any products and services they offer. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such websites. You are responsible for knowing when you are leaving our website to visit a third party website, and for reading and understanding the terms of use and privacy policy statements for each such third party website.

### Terms and Conditions

To understand fully the terms and conditions that apply to your use of this website, please read our Terms and Conditions, which may be found by clicking on the “Terms & Conditions” link located at the bottom of this webpage and at https://arqspin.com/terms-conditions. By using this website, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to comply with our Terms and Conditions and this Privacy Policy.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email us at support@arqspin.com. You may also reach us by mail at: Arqball LLC, 313 2nd Street SE #110, Charlottesville, Virginia 22902.
